Theoretically, it is possible.
（真帆(まほ)）理論上は確かに可能よ
However, that's just in theory.
ただし あくまで理論上
The mental burden alone will
be colossal... to go back to 2011.
精神的な負担は計り知れないわ
2011年まで…
Even with the improvements that
make it possible to leap two weeks at once...
（真帆）改良を加えて
一度に２週間ずつ―
さかのぼれる
といっても―
...in order to go back one year,
you'll have to time leap over 20 times.
それでも
１年戻るために―
20回以上タイムリープを
繰り返さなきゃならない
Part way through, it'll be 48 hours.
途中からは48時間
A leap will take you just two days back.
２日前までしか戻れなくなるわ
そうなったら…
Which means...
It'll take some 3,000 time leaps...
（岡部(おかべ)）3,000回の
タイムリープが必要になる
That's an absurd amount...
（真帆）
途方もない数字ね
You're really going?
（ダル）本当に行くん？
Yeah.
ああ
I have no other choice...
それしかないからな
この世界を変えるには
...if I'm to change this world.
Looks like you're set on going.
決意は固いみたいね
Long time no see, Okabe Rintaro.
（アマデウス紅莉栖(くりす)）
久しぶりね 岡部倫太郎(りんたろう)さん
[Kurisu]?!
紅莉栖…
The entire time you were in a coma,
she was monitoring you day and night.
こん睡状態になっている
岡部さんを―
ずっとモニタリングしていて
くれたのが―
彼女なのよ
Amadeus was?
アマデウスが？
I can't exactly fight,
so it's the least I could do.
（アマデウス紅莉栖）
私は戦えないから せめて… ね
But still, for 11 whole years?
（岡部）それにしても
11年もの間？
Time is irrelevant. That sort
of supervision is no work for me.
どれだけ長くても―
機械的に
管理するだけなら―
負担もないわよ
Also, she'll be your partner
for your long time leap journey.
（真帆）そして―
これからのあなたの
長いタイムリープの旅の協力者
あ？
No matter how many times you leap back...
（真帆）
これから あなたが―
何度タイムリープを
しても―
...up until 2025, each time you wake up,
she'll be right there for you.
２０２５年までは―
目覚めたときには
必ず近くに彼女がいる
When you woke up this time,
you broke my terminal though.
（アマデウス紅莉栖）
今回は目覚めたあなたに―
端末を壊されちゃって…
あっ…
After you wake up...
目覚めたあと 私に―
...if you tell me you came via time leap,
I'll do what I can to help.
“タイムリープしてきた”と
話してくれれば―
私は協力するはずよ
Just say you wanna get back to 2011.
“2011年まで戻りたい”って
フッ…
What?
（アマデウス紅莉栖）何？
Nothing, it's just...
（岡部）いや 昔 似たようなことを
話していたなと思い出してな
I remembered a conversation
like this from a long time ago.
No longer... will I run.
（岡部）俺は もう逃げない
Mayuri once said...
まゆりは言ってくれた
...it wasn't right to push everything on me.
全てを俺に押しつけないでと
Somewhere along the line,
her kindness became my excuse.
どこかで その優しさを
言い訳にしていた
However...
だが…
I only stand here right
now because of everyone.
今 俺が ここに立っているのは
みんなのおかげだ
Because they were there...
みんながいてくれて―
Because they never gave up, I'm here.
みんなが諦めなかったからこその
今だ
It wasn't forced on me alone.
俺が１人背負うんじゃない
Because I want to carry it too.
俺も背負いたいんだ
It's everyone's future.
みんなの未来を
Ready?
（ダル）いいん？
Do it.
やってくれ
うっ…
うおおおお…
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
Rinascimento
of
Image
Formation
Return of
Phoenix
ハッ！
（岡部）ハァ… ハァ…
あっ ううっ…
うっ…
（アマデウス紅莉栖）
あっ 岡部？　意識が戻ったの!?
Okabe? You're awake?
Okabe, don't move so quickly.
岡部 急に動かないで！
For the past 11 years,
you've been out cold in a coma.
あなたは11年の間 こん睡状態で
意識が戻らなかったの
You shouldn't be—
無理をしては…
Listen to me...
（岡部）聞いてくれ
えっ？
Hmm?
I time leaped here
from two weeks in the future.
俺は２週間後から
タイムリープしてきた
Huh?
はあ？
Time leaped...?
タイムリープって…
Curse you, five-hours-from-now me...!
（紅莉栖）恨むぞ ５時間後の私
Listen...
（岡部）聞いてくれ
俺は２週間後から
タイムリープマシンを使って―
I used the time leap machine to
come here from two weeks in the future.
ここに来たんだ
I met Daru and Hiyajo too.
ダルや比屋定(ひやじょう)さんにも会った
It's now the year 2036, and I heard
all about what the world's become...
2036年の今―
世界がどうなってしまったのかも
聞いている
And you...
お前が…
And you... You've been watching
over me for the past 11 years.
お前が この11年間 俺の面倒を
ずっと見ていてくれたことも
Eh? U-Uh...
へ？　あっ…
I-I find it hard to believe, but...
に にわかには信じられないけど…
Believe me. It's the truth.
信じてくれ 本当なんだ
You're really... from the future?
本当に？　未来から…
I need a favor.
頼みがある
Okabe?
（るか）岡部… さん
Kyouma!
（フェイリス）凶真(きょうま)！
Sorry to worry you two.
心配かけたな ２人とも
Okabe!
（るか）岡部さん！
（フェイリス）凶真！
Kyouma!
Okarin!
（ダル）オカリン！
It's true, you really woke up!
（真帆）本当に気がついたのね！
Daru, Hiyajo...
ダル 比屋定さん
Did you hear from Amadeus?
アマデウスから連絡はきているか？
Y-Yeah.
（ダル）あ ああ…
（真帆）本気なの？
Are you serious? To go back to 2011...
2011年まで戻るなんて
I know full well that it'll
take about 3,000 time leaps.
約3,000回のタイムリープが
必要になることは分かっている
（２人）あ…
But, you're really...?
あなた 本当に…
Okarin.
オカリン…
Please.
（岡部）頼む
I guess this means you'll be having
this same conversation over and over.
（真帆）これからも
何度も同じ会話を繰り返すのね
Every time you time leap...
タイムリープするたびに
Not only that, but he'll taste the pain
of waking from a long sleep each time.
（アマデウス紅莉栖）それに
長い眠りから覚める苦しみも―
毎回 味わうことになる
You sure about this?
本当に いいの？
Okabe...
（るか）岡部さん…
Rukako.
（岡部）ルカ子(こ)
（るか）は はい
Y-Yes?
There's no such thing as a fixed future.
確定した未来なんてない
Never give up.
諦めるな
A path will open for sure.
道は きっと切り開ける
ハッ！
あ…
Okabe? You're awake?
岡部？　意識が戻ったの!?
You say, "Don't move so quickly".
（岡部）お前は―
急に…
Don't move—
“急に動かないで”
And that "For the past 11 years,
you've been out cold in a coma".
“11年間 こん睡状態で
意識が戻らなかったのに”と言う
あっ あなた…
You...
（真帆）ここから先は
これまでのようにはいかないわ
You won't be able to
leap like you have till now.
Because two weeks before today,
you're not even here.
今から２週間前の過去に
あなたは ここにいない
Where was I?
どこにいる？
I don't know.
（真帆）分からない
（岡部）えっ…
Two weeks ago, you were caught
by the peacekeeping squad.
（真帆）今から２週間前
あなたは治安部隊に捕まったのよ
It wasn't until yesterday that we
rescued you and found you in a stupor.
そして私たちが廃人になった
あなたを救出できたのが―
ちょうど昨日
So... other than today
and that one day two weeks ago...
つまり 今日の この日と
２週間前の２日間以外は…
You won't be able to time leap.
（ダル）タイムリープはできない
Doubt you'll get a chance to take
a call once you're captured either.
捕まったあとのオカリンが
通話に出れるとは思えないし
You can't until you're
rescued and carried here...
（真帆）救出されたあと
ここに運び込まれて―
...and you're connected to the
monitoring terminal and Amadeus.
モニター用の端子と
アマデウスに接続されるまでは…
Sorry.
（ダル）ごめん…
（岡部）ん？
If only we were quicker by one more day
and got you out of there sooner.
（ダル）僕らが
せめて あと１日早く―
オカリンを助け出せていれば―
We could've sent you off
with plenty of time to spare...
もっと余裕のあるタイミングで
送ってあげられたのに
In that case, I'm equally at fault for not
improving the time leap machine.
それを言うなら―
タイムリープマシンの改良が
できなかった私も同罪よ
The best I could do was two weeks.
私の技術では どうしても２週間
336時間 戻るのが限界なの
336 hours isn't nearly good enough.
It's frustrating.
悔しいわ
That's not true.
そんなことはない
I'm actually grateful you
managed a two-week time leap.
むしろよく２週間のタイムリープを
可能にしてくれた
Even Kurisu was stuck
with 48 hours as her limit.
紅莉栖でもタイムリープは
48時間が限界だったんだ
You should be proud of yourself.
君は胸を張ってくれていい
Yeah!
（フェイリス）うん！
That's not my only worry.
（真帆）懸念は まだある
If the time leap machine alters
the world line even slightly...
タイムリープマシンでも僅かに
世界線が変動するとすれば―
今の この状況が破壊され
本当に死ぬことになるかもしれない
...this current situation might be ruined
and you actually could end up dead.
It might change the past.
それが過去を変えるということ
I know.
（岡部）分かってる
Even so, I'm going back.
（岡部）それでも戻る
I've come 11 years since 2036,
2036年から11年 数百という
タイムリープを繰り返し―
done hundreds of time leaps,
and with the help of my friends
from year after year, reached where I am.
全ての時代のみんなに
協力してもらい ここまで来た
Okarin!
（由季(ゆき)）オカリンさん！
I'm glad you're all right!
（由季）ご無事だったんですね
Yuki and...
由季さんと…
Listen here!
聞いてくれ！
You've all fought with all of your hearts,
no matter the time or place.
どんなときでも
みんなは精いっぱい戦っていた
So please, don't give up!
だから諦めないでくれ
The future...
未来は絶対 変えてみせる！
...I'll show you it can be changed!
Do it!
（岡部）やってくれ
（ダル）いくお
Here we go!
うっ… うおおおお…
（ダル）オカリン！
Okarin!
Kyouma! We're heading
for the rendezvous point!
（フェイリス）凶真 みんなは
合流ポイントに向かったニャ
Hurry there, meow!
凶真も急ぐニャ！
Faris...
（岡部）フェイリス…
Okabe?
岡部？
作戦行動中じゃなかったの？
Isn't the operation in progress?
Listen to me.
（岡部）聞いてくれ
俺は未来からタイムリープしてきた
I time leaped here from the future.
（アマデウス紅莉栖）はあ!?
Huh?
It might be hard for you to believe,
but there's no time.
（岡部）信じられないのは
しかたがない
だが時間がない
俺を信じて教えてくれ
Trust me, I need your help.
Wh-What?
なっ 何を？
Today... I end up getting caught by
the Bureau, tortured by them, and die.
（岡部）今日 俺は このあと
管理局に捕らえられて―
拷問を受けて死ぬ
What should I do?
どうすればいい？
What can I do... to escape from that fate?
どうやったら
その運命から逃れられると思う？
We know why you get caught.
（アマデウス紅莉栖）
あなたが なぜ捕まったのか―
We heard it directly from you.
私たちは あなたから聞いていた
Okabe Rintaro dies in 2025.
岡部倫太郎が 2025年に死ぬと
Up until now, you've used that
to your advantage and lived.
あなたは これまで―
それを逆手に取って生き延びてきた
If today is that day...
今日という日が
その日だというなら―
...the world line convergence you've had
as your ally finally turns the tables on you.
今まで味方してくれていた
世界線の収束が―
よってたかって あなたに牙をむく
No matter what you do...
どんな選択をしようとも
世界線は収束し―
...the world line will converge
and you'll end up captured.
あなたが捕らえられるという
結果になってしまう
それでも…
Even so...
Okabe.
（アマデウス紅莉栖）岡部
Think you can give me ten minutes?
私に10分 時間をちょうだい
I've got a plan.
策がある
All right.
分かった
In that ten minutes...
（アマデウス紅莉栖）
その10間分で―
...memorize this map with the enemy positions.
この地図と敵の配置を覚えて
Huh? What's the meaning of this?
は？　おい どういうことだ？
Typically, I'm the one navigating you to safety.
（アマデウス紅莉栖）
いつもどおりなら―
あなたを私がナビゲートして
脱出していた
But if we assume this is a trap,
there's a high probability that
でも これがワナだとするなら
私を持っていること自体が―
the fact that I'm with you
is responsible for your death.
あなたの死因になる可能性が
非常に高い
だから…
So...
Uninstall the Amadeus app?!
（岡部）アマデウスの
アプリを落とす？
（岡部の荒い息）
Just in case, remove your radio battery too.
（アマデウス紅莉栖）念のため
通信器の電源も落として
It might be enough to confuse them.
少しは目を
くらませられるかもしれない
Also...
そのうえで…
Use them as decoys?!
みんなをおとりに？
そんなこと…
I refuse to—
Calm down!
（アマデウス紅莉栖）落ち着いて！
You came here from 2036,
time leaping the entire way.
あなたは2036年から―
タイムリープを繰り返して
ここまで来た
Right?
そうよね？
Yeah...
ああ
Therefore, you've witnessed
they're alive in the future.
（アマデウス紅莉栖）
なら あなたは―
未来のみんなを観測している
They can't die here.
死ぬことはありえない
あっ しかし…
B-But...!
（フェイリス）大丈夫ニャ 凶真！
It's okay, meow, Kyouma!
クーニャンに聞いたニャ
Kuu-meow filled us in.
We're all running circles around the city, meow!
今 みんなで街じゅうを
バラバラに動いてるニャ！
Kyouma should run straight for Akiba
and get to the time leap machine, meow!
凶真は まっすぐ―
秋葉原(あきはばら)のタイムリープマシン
目がけて走るニャ！
It's too dangerous! You can't—
危険だ！　それは…
Okarin!
（ダル）オカリン！
ここは僕らを信じてくれなのだぜ
This is where you've gotta believe in us, dude.
Daru...
（岡部）ダル…
The target's marker disappeared.
（オペレーター）
ターゲットのマーカーが消えました
They're gone from GPS.
ＧＰＳからもロスト
He had to have disconnected Amadeus.
アマデウスシステムを
切断したようです
Teams 1 and 2, head for that area, pronto.
（オペレーター）
チーム１ チーム２を―
ロストポイントへ急行させます
Our priority is capturing the target.
（オペレーター）
ターゲットの捕獲を最優先
Ignore the rest of Valkyrie if needed.
ほかのワルキューレの部隊は
無視して構わない
As long as Okabe Rintaro—
岡部倫太郎だけを…
Target acquired!
（オペレーター）
ターゲットを再確認！
Wait, this is...?
（オペレーター）
ですが… これは？
What's wrong?
（レスキネン）どうした？
岡部倫太郎のマーカーが
複数 現れました！
There're multiple Okabe Rintaro markers!
Two? Three?!
They're coming up all over the place!
（オペレーター）２つ… ３つ？
いや 反対側のエリアにも
現れたぞ！
What's that mean?!
（オペレーター）どういうことだ!?
I-I don't know!
（オペレーター）わ 分かりません
突然 アマデウスからの反応が…
Out of nowhere, Amadeus just popped up!
Lintahlo...
（レスキネン）リンターロ…
I'll no longer give up.
（岡部）俺は もう諦めない
I'll no longer lie to myself.
自分にウソをつくことも―
I'll no longer pretend I made the right
choice... and I'll no longer compromise!
これが正しいだなんて言い聞かせて
妥協することも決してしない！
They've all been desperately battling on,
driven by the hope to change our world.
みんなが必死であらがい 戦い―
この世界を変えようとしてきた思い
I'll believe in their hope.
その思いを俺は信じる
Hope... will be my strength!
思いは力になる
I'll show everyone we can reach that place!
絶対に そこへ
たどりついてみせる！
Okarin.
（ダル）オカリン
Uncle Okarin.
（鈴羽(すずは)）オカリンおじさん
（萌郁(もえか)）岡部君
Okabe.
Kyouma!
（フェイリス）凶真
（るか）岡部さん
Okabe.
Okarin.
（かがり）オカリンさん
Okarin!
（まゆり）オカリン
Okabe.
岡部！
I will!
俺はー！
（岡部の荒い息）
（岡部）うおおおお！
（岡部）ハァ ハァ…
（ダル）オカリン
Okarin?
What's going on?
（真帆）急にどうしたの？
（岡部の荒い息）
Daru...
（岡部）ダル 比屋定さん
Huh?
Hiyajo.
Punch me!
俺を殴れ
Eh? A-Again?
え？　ま また？
Wh-What are you talking—
（真帆）な 何を言ってるの？
（岡部）遠慮はいらない
No need to hold back.
Think of all the anger
you've pent up because of me.
今まで俺に対して
思っていた憤り
Your feelings for Suzuha...
鈴羽への思い
Take it all and punch me with it!
その全てをぶつけて 俺を殴れ
What's this about?
どういうこと？
It's deserved.
（岡部）これはケジメだ
I've had my head buried in the sand.
今まで見て見ぬふりをしてきた
I've been running in fear and I deserve it!
恐怖から逃げてきた
この俺のケジメだ！
あ… 本当に… いいん？
Are you really... sure?
Hashida?!
橋田(はしだ)さん!?
あっ…
（岡部）ああ
Yeah.
（ダル）んん…
Do it!
やってくれ！　あっ…
Ah!
（真帆）ああっ…
Uh...
（ダル）あ…
Okabe!
岡部さん!?
（岡部）フッ フフ フフフ…
Eh?
（真帆･ダル）え？
That did the trick...
（岡部）効いたぞ
I expected no less a slug
from my favorite right arm...
さすが我がフェイバリット
ライトアームの１発だ
Eh?!
I... have time leaped back from the future.
俺はタイムリープで
未来から帰ってきた
えっ？
Eh?
Okarin?
（ダル）オカリン？
You're so wrong, Daru!
（岡部）違うぞ ダル…
（ダル）あ…
（真帆）はっ？
Huh?
（岡部）フッ フフフ…
（岡部）フゥーッ フフフ…
（ダル）その笑い…
That laugh!
（岡部）フフッ
フフフ… ハハハ…
Huh?
（真帆）はあ？
（岡部）
フゥーッ ハッハハハハ…
ハハハハハッ…
（岡部のせき込み）
ハハハハハッ アハハハハ…
My name is...
我が名は凶真
...Kyouma!
（真帆）凶真？
Kyou... ma?
Yes.
（岡部）そう
Lab Member 001!
ラボメンナンバー001！
The founder of this lab...
このラボの創設者にして―
The seeker of chaos, the destroyer
of this world's ruling structure...
混とんを望み
世界の支配構造を覆す―
狂気のマッドサイエンティスト！
The mad scientist...
（真帆）え～？
（ダル）ああ…
Hououin... Kyouma!
鳳凰院(ほうおういん)凶真だ！
O-Okabe...?
お… 岡部さん？
Okarin!
（ダル）オカリン！
（真帆）え!?
Eh?!
You, the Loli Girl!
（岡部）そこのロリっ子！
Huh?
（真帆）は？
（岡部）お前だ！
Yes, you!
Who else here is a Loli Girl but you?!
この場にロリっ子といえば
お前しかいないだろう！
Bring my lab coat! At once!
白衣を持て！　今すぐにだ！
（真帆）な… 何なのよ もう
（岡部）そう
Wh-What the heck?
Aha!
Behold my sacred, silvery armor!
これこそが
我が聖なる白銀(しろがね)のよろい！
The moment my hands slide through
these sleeves, I truly awake from my slumber!
これに袖を通した その瞬間
我は真に眠りから覚めるのだ
フゥーッ ハッハッハ…
（ダル）ああ…
（真帆）あの 橋田さん これって…
Um, Hashida? What's this?
He's gone back... to the old Okarin!
戻ったんだお 前のオカリンに
（真帆）えっ…
Eh?
When he's nutty and nonsensical...
and has out-of-control delusions!
（ダル）ムチャクチャで
支離滅裂で―
手がつけられない厨二病(ちゅうにびょう)な
僕らのリーダーのオカリンに！
He's back to our leader, Okarin!
You both will complete the time leap machine.
（岡部）
タイムリープマシンは完成する
Eh?
My being here is proof of that.
ここにいる俺自身が証しだ
Loli Girl!
（岡部）ロリっ子よ！
（真帆）ロリっ子 言うな！
Don't call me that!
As of today, I grant thee
the title of Lab Member 009!
貴様には これより―
ラボメンナンバー009の
称号を与える
You are now a hand of Hououin Kyouma
and shall aid our operations!
以後 この鳳凰院凶真の手足となり
オペレーションに参加するがうぃ～
ヒヤジョセフィーヌよ
Hiyajo Safina.
Wh-Who the hell's that?!
（真帆）ちょっ 何よ それ！
これより！　円卓会議を実施する！
As of now, I call a round table meeting!
Summon all lab members immediately!
すぐにラボメンを招集するのだ！
What's going on, meow?
（フェイリス）
一体 どうしたニャ？
Who knows...?
（るか）さあ あの…
Um... Could you explain
why we're here today, Okabe—
一体 今日は
何の集まりなんですか？
（るか）岡部さ…
（岡部）凶真だ！
It's Kyouma!
（フェイリス）あ…
A new operation is about to commence.
（岡部）これより
新たなるオペレーションを開始する
For it to succeed,
all lab members must do their part.
この作戦にはラボメン全員の
協力が必要だ
Where's Mayuri and Suzuha?
（るか）まゆりちゃんと
鈴羽さんは？
Moe-meow sent a message that she's busy, meow.
モエニャンも用事があるとか
メールが来たニャ
Uh, Shiina and—
あっ 椎名(しいな)さんたちは…
Never fear.
（岡部）案ずるでない！
全て想定の範囲内だ
It's all within expectation.
Nevertheless, the operation will continue.
そのうえで
このオペレーションは実行される
Oh! So the red star I saw
yesterday in the western sky was...
ハッ！
だとすると―
昨日 西の空に見えた
赤き星は…
（岡部）作戦名は
オペレーション･ベガ！
I hereby name it... Operation Vega!
（岡部）作戦名は
オペレーション･ベガ！
Recover Amadeus's data?
（真帆）アマデウスのデータを
奪還する？
Yes, confirm if you must.
そうだ 確認してみるがいい
She's already left messages on @channel
and Leskinen has taken her away.
既に @ちゃんねるに
メッセージを残し―
レスキネンの手によって
隔離されている
Huh? The professor? Why would he...?
（真帆）は？　教授が？
何で そんな…
It's real! The occult board got hacked!
（ダル）マジだ！
オカ板(いた)が
クラッキングされているお
The Organization has showed its hand
and is jamming phone signals in Akihabara.
既に秋葉原全域には―
機関の手によって
妨害電波が張り巡らされている
However... Faris!
だが… フェイリスよ！
ニャ！
Meow?
Deploy the neighborhood
watch around the Radio Building!
（岡部）今すぐに
ラジ館の周りに自警団を！
They should spot several
suspicious foreigners in the area.
怪しい動きをしている外国人が
多数 見つかるはずだ
Relay us info on all of them!
片っ端から通報しろ！
We'll have to rely on pay phones!
公衆電話を使えばいけるはずだ
分かったニャ！
Roger, meow!
R-Radio Building?!
ラ… ラジ館って
I know that Part-time Warrior
and Mayuri are heading there.
バイト戦士とまゆりが
既に向かっているのは知っている
（真帆･ダル）あっ…
W-We've gotta stop them!
（真帆）と… 止めないと！
Even if we stopped them, it'll likely end
the same way because of convergence.
仮に止めたとしても―
収束によって
同じ結果となる可能性が高い
If there's any way to stop them, yes...
もしも２人を救うのならば！
ああ…
Eh?
えっ？
（岡部）ああ 俺だ
Yes, it's me.
そう オペレーションの目的は
ただ１つ
Right... The operation has one sole objective.
To ensure Mayuri and
Suzuha are safely sent to the past.
まゆりと鈴羽を無事に
過去へと旅立たせること
分かっている
I know... I won't repeat that mistake again.
絶対に もう繰り返させはしない
El. Psy. Congroo.
エル･プサイ･コングルゥ
Mr. Braun!
（岡部）ミスター･ブラウン！
Huh?
（天王寺(てんのうじ)）あ？
What's with you? The second
I think you're almost normal...
何だ おめえ
少しはマシになったと思ったら…
I don't have time to explain the details.
詳しいことを話している暇はない！
This phone outage is the Organization's doing.
この電波障害は組織の仕業だ
Stratfor.... DURPA...
ストラトフォー ＤＵＲＰＡ(ダーパ)
協力を仰ぎたい
I seek your assistance, Mr. Ferdinand Braun.
ミスター･
フェルディナント･ブラウン
Well?
どう？
Just like Okarin said, it's been taken away.
（ダル）オカリンの言うとおり
確かに隔離されているお
But if I can just find out where...
でも場所さえ分かれば…
I'll leave your tea right here.
お茶 置いておきますね
Thanks.
ありがとう
Don't mention it. I can't do much else...
いえ 僕には このくらいしか…
That's not true at all.
（真帆）そんなことないわ
さっき あの人も
言っていたでしょう
Remember what he was saying earlier?
Rukako, I need you to
support the mechanic members.
ルカ子は２人のメカニックメンの
サポートを頼む
Support?
（るか）サポート？
（岡部）ああ
Yes... It's a vital mission requiring
consideration and a stout heart.
気配りと心の強さが必要な
重要な任務だ
（るか）あ…
I wondered why everyone was so happy
to see that Okabe back, but...
何で みんなが あんな岡部さんを
喜ぶのか不思議だったけど―
少し分かったような気がするわ
I think I see why now.
Hell yeah!
（ダル）キター！
Make no mistake, I found it!
間違いなし 見つけたお！
Mission complete!
ミッションコンプリート！
Urushibara, get the word out!
漆原(うるしばら)さん すぐに連絡を！
Right!
はい！
You have one missed call.
（音声アナウンス）
新しいメッセージは１件です
Hello, Kyouma?
（るか）もしもし 凶真さん？
Hashida just found Amadeus
and should recover it shortly.
今 橋田さんが
アマデウスを見つけて―
すぐ回収するそうです
He said not to worry.
“心配するな”って
Good, with this...
（岡部）よし これで
Wait for me, Mayuri...
待っていてくれ まゆり…
I will save you.
必ず助ける
鈴(すず)さん？　痛っ…
Suzu...
Ouch!
（鈴羽）じっとして
Stay still. That ricochet may have
just grazed you, but you're still bleeding.
跳弾が かすめただけだけど
出血はあるから
（拍手）
（２人）あっ…
Excellent!
（レスキネン）エクセレント
To think she'd clean up all on her own...
まさか１人で片づけてしまうとは…
The future's brainwashing
techniques sure are incredible.
未来の洗脳技術は
やはり すばらしい
You're...
（鈴羽）お前は!?　あっ…
You did this... to Kagari!
お前が かがりを…
（レスキネン）そうだよ
ワルキューレの橋田鈴羽君
That's right, Valkyrie's Hashida Suzuha.
Kagari was a spy long before
the day you left on your journey with her.
かがりは あの日―
君と旅立つ前から
スパイとなっていたんだよ
未来の私の手によってね
That is, courtesy of the future me.
Your anger is justified, though
I don't have the time to entertain it.
怒りは ごもっとも
だが それをぶつける時間は
もうない
（鈴羽）うっ…
I'll make it easy on you.
（レスキネン）楽にしてあげよう
Soon, you won't have to think
about the bitter future or painful past.
もう つらい未来も
苦しい過去も―
見なくて済むように
Or perhaps... you'd like
for me to wipe clean your mind?
それとも―
私の手で忘れさせてあげようか？
That's right. A little tampering
with your brain and...?
なあに
脳を少し触らせてもらえば…
ホワット？
What?
Lintahlo...
リンターロ？
Uncle Okarin?
オカリンおじさん？
Okarin!
オカリン？
あ…
（レスキネン）
なぜ 君がここにいる？
How is it that you're here, Lintahlo?
リンターロ 誰から…
Who told—
Kagari won't be coming.
（岡部）かがりは ここには来ない
Because... we've already restrained her.
（岡部）既に我々が拘束した
You may not have realized it, but we've
taken measures around the Radio Building.
あなたは知らないだろうが―
ラジ館周りも
既に手は打たせてもらった
Mr. Leskinen.
ミスター･レスキネン
You may have thought yourself
as a god who could see through everything, but...
自らを
全てを見通せる神と―
思っていたかも
しれないが―
...I'm afraid to say all
your schemes have been foiled.
その策略は全て
打ち破らせてもらったぞ
Lintahlo, what are you...?
（レスキネン）
リンターロ 君は…
What do you think you're—
君は何を言って…
（レスキネン）ああっ…
Okarin?
（まゆり）オカリン？
Lab Member 002... Shiina Mayuri!
（岡部）
ラボメンナンバー００２
椎名まゆりよ
Operation Arclight.
オペレーション･
アークライト
あ…
（岡部）俺は
タイムリープしてきた
I time leaped to come here.
I know all about it.
全て知ってる
Okarin...
（まゆり）オカリン…
In less than 30 minutes,
this place becomes a war zone.
（岡部）ここは あと
30分もしないうちに―
戦場になる
Hurry!
急げ！
Uncle Okarin!
オカリンおじさん？
I'll somehow deal with Kagari!
（岡部）かがりは
俺が何とかする
Take care of Mayuri.
まゆりを頼む
Okarin...
オカリン…
All right.
分かった
With this, they should make it in time.
（岡部）
これで間に合うはずだ
The time machine will vanish
to the past... following history...
タイムマシンは
過去へと消える
歴史どおり…
With this...
これで…
（岡部）なっ!?
Impossible! It's too early!
バカな！　早すぎる！
ハッ！
Mayuri!
まゆりー！